Preliminary Guide to the Craufurd D. W. Goodwin papers, 1960-2010 UA.29.02.0010
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2017-0030, 1990-2010, undated; 4
  - Reprints (by Goodwin and others) (Box 58)
  - Loose materials (Box 58)
  - Correspondence (Box 59)
  - Reprints (articles by Goodwin) (Box 59)
  - Lecture notes (Box 59)
  - Lecture notes (Box 60)
  - Partial manuscript (by Goodwin?) (Box 60)
  - Poster for Bloomsbury exhibit at Nasher Museum (Box 60)
  - Materials labeled "For Magog" (Box 60)